Mi-chan.
み ー ちゃん
cute?
かわいい?
That's amazing, I'm curious about those breasts.
すごいさ、気になってるの、そのお胸が
I caught a glimpse of it a while ago,
さっきなんかチラッと見かけたけど、
It's huge.
でかいよね
Yeah.
うん
Not really, maybe because it's clothes, but it doesn't really get emphasized,
あんまりね、なんか服だからか、あんまり強調されてないけど、
It's scary to see it up close.
近くで見たらやばいね
I would like to ask you a few questions, but
ちょっといろいろ質問してもいいですが、
How old are you now?
今はいくつなの?
I'm 18 now, and yesterday was my birthday.
今、18で、昨日、誕生日です
I turned 18 yesterday.
昨日、18になったわ
Congratulations!
おめでとう!
Ah, yesterday!
あ、昨日!
It was just a flow.
ギリギリ流れだったんだ
If it had been a little longer, I would have been 17 years old.
もうちょっとだったら17歳だったのね
Yeah, I wanted to.
え たかったね
Did you eat cake?
ケーキ食べた?
I ate cake.
ケーキ食べた
Did you eat it?
食べた?
Did you celebrate?
お祝いしたの?
I had them celebrate.
お祝いしてもらった
Did you celebrate?
お祝いしたの?
Yeah.
うん
nice.
いいね
Like your mother.
お母さんとか
Well, are you going to school now?
え、今はじゃあ、学校行ってんの?
Yeah, I'm going.
うん、行ってます
How old are you?
何年生?
3 years?
3年か
High 3?
高3?
It's kind of like that, it looks like you have a half-Japanese face.
なんかあれだね、顔立ちハーフっぽいよね
My mother is Korean.
お母さんが韓国人
Oh, I'm half Korean.
あ、韓国のハーフなんだ
Is your father Japanese?
お 父 さんは日本人?
My father is Japanese.
お父さんは日本人です
I see.
そうか
Have you lived in Korea?
韓国住んでたりしたの?
Japan.
日本
I lived in Korea until I was in elementary school, and then I came here from Korea and went to elementary school there.
小学生の前まで韓国で、韓国からこっち来て小学校行って
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Oh, then can you talk?
え、じゃあ喋れる?
I can't speak.
喋れない
Oh, you can talk, right?
え、喋れるでしょ?
I can't speak, I can't speak.
喋れない、喋れない
lie?
うそ?
Can't you have a daily conversation?
日常会話できんじゃない?
I can't.
できない
I only know the name of the dish.
料理の名前しか分からない
I just don't know, just a little bit.
ちょっと、ちょっとね、しか分からない
Do you have any memories of Korea?
韓国の記憶ある?
Memories of Korea...
韓国の記憶...
Not at all.
全然ない
I forgot.
忘れちゃいました
There's nothing.
なんもないんだ
Which one do you like?
どっちが好き?
Do you like Japan?
日本の好き?
South Korea.
韓国
I prefer Korea.
韓国の方が好き
Well, I like Korea better.
え、韓国の方が好きだね
Because it's cool.
かっこいいから
An idol.
アイドルが
Ah, I like K-POP.
あ、K-POP好きなんだ
Well, who do you like?
え、誰が好きとか?
The upper half of Sebuchi.
せぶちの上半
Ah, I don't understand at all.
あ、全然分かんないけど
It's really cool.
めっちゃかっこいい
cool.
かっこいい
It's cool, though.
かっこいいよ、でも
Korean wave, idols.
韓流、アイドルってね
Be slender.
スラッとしてね
I see.
そっか
I love Korea.
韓国好きなんだ
Well, what are you going to do after graduation?
え、卒業後はどうするの?
course.
進路
After graduation...
卒業後は...
Just a little more.
もうちょっとしょ
I really like it.
めっちゃ好きじゃん
What, are you going?
え、行くの?
Is it decided?
決まり?
I feel like I want to go there once.
一回行きたいな、みたいな
It's decided.
決まった
決まりました
Study abroad?
留学?
What do you mean?
ってこと?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you going alone?
一人で行くの?
I'm alone.
一人です
nice.
いいね
I'm going to study beauty.
美容学びに行くの
But that doesn't mean I can't talk right now, right?
でも、今喋れないわけでしょ?
I can't speak.
喋れない
So I'm studying a lot right now.
だから、今めっちゃ勉強してます
勉強中?
勉強中
Isn't it difficult?
難しくない?
It's Korean.
韓国語って
It's difficult, but I don't know what to write in Hangul.
難しいけど、 ハングルとか、何書いてるかわかんないよ、
That.
あれ
I really don't know.
ほんとわかんない
I didn't understand, seriously.
わかんなかった、まじで
I really don't understand.
本当にわかんなくて
So, I was asked to work with various teachers.
で、なんか、いろいろ先生とかつけてもらって
gentlemen?
先生?
A cram school?
塾とか?
Homeschooling.
家庭教
Do Korean teachers teach you at home?
韓国の先生、家庭教つけてんの?
Okay, so the house looks nice.
結構、じゃあ、なんか家が良さそうだね
Is the house good?
家が良い?
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
You were doing some lessons, right?
習い事とかしてたでしょ?
You did quite well.
結構やったね
What were you doing?
何やってた?
Volleyball, swimming, and the number one,
バレーと、あとは、水泳とか、空番とか、
Slim.
修身
You're doing a lot.
めっちゃやってんな
So, this is how I did it.
で、こうやってました
I see.
そうか
Do you have a boyfriend now?
彼氏いんの、今?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
not present?
いない?
That seems erotic.
エロそうだね
Have you ever had sex?
エッチしたことあるでしょ?
there is.
あります
Yes, there is.
あるよね
How many people did you have sex with?
何 人くらい、エッチした?
I don't know because I haven't counted.
数えてないから分かんない
If you're not counting, you must be doing a lot.
数えてないって、めっちゃしてんじゃんよ、
Well then.
それじゃあ
That's it, in the first place.
そんな、そもそも
How much?
どんぐらいなの?
Do you go often?
結構行く?
Eh, what do you think?
えー、どうなんだ
Are you ready to go to 20 or 30?
もう、20とか30とか行っちゃう?
No, I don't know, I don't know.
いや、分かんない、分かんない
picture?
え?
Because I'm not counting.
数えてないから
What is that? Who are you talking with?
何それ、誰とすんの、そんな
people around you.
周りの人
What about the people around me?
何、周りの人って
Friends from school.
学校の友達とか
he,
他、
Someone nearby.
近 くにいる人で
Do you do it one by one with each person nearby?
近くにいる人ずつ、やっちゃうの?
picture?
え?
But men too, you know, when they see breasts,
でも、男もさ、そのね、おっぱい見たら、
I'll pocket it.
ポッケしちゃうよね
Do you want to meet someone from Korea?
韓国の人とはやんないの?
Once in a while.
たまーに
Oh, are you going to do it?
あ、やるの?
Once in a while.
たまーに
Aren't you going to do that with your private tutor?
それ、家庭教師の人とやっちゃうんじゃないの?
Make it tama.
たまーにする
Shall we do it?
やっちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to do it with a tutor?
家庭教師とやっちゃうの?
I'll do it.
やっちゃう
At home?
家で?
Don't you have a mother at home?
家にお母さんとかいるんじゃないの?
There are, but only on the first and second floors.
いるけど、1階と2階ばかり
While your mom is on the first floor?
お母さんが1階にいる間に?
A naughty girl.
とんだすけべえ少女
I'm going to do some naughty things today.
ちょっと今日いろいろ、すけべしちゃうよ
So cute.
かわちい
Being a cram school teacher is really dangerous.
塾の先生ってやっぱやばいよ、それ
But for five years, I've been studying all my life, dressing like this.
でも5年一生、勉強さ、こういう格好でやってるの、
First class.
初授業
It makes me horny.
ムラムラするやね
Put it away?
しまう?
Are you seducing me?
誘惑するの?
Not at all, not at all.
全然、全然
Now, give me your breasts.
これでさ、おっぱいをさ、俺がさ、
This is how you taught them side by side.
横でこうやって教えたわけでしょ
What if I teach you about breasts?
おっぱいを教えつけてきたらすんの?
No, I won't.
いや、私からはしない
What do you mean by me?
私からはどういうこと?
I won't do it, but it's true.
私からはしないけど、当たっちゃう
how?
どう やって?
Try it.
やってみて
Like this.
こうやって
You're doing it.
やっててんじゃん
different.
違う
You're doing it.
やっててんじゃん
You'll get it right, like this.
当たっちゃう、こうやって
You're doing it.
やってんじゃん
Because it's close.
近いから
How do you get so close to each other?
こうやって、こんなに密着するの?
Yeah.
うん
With the teacher?
先生と?
Yeah.
うん
Moreover, the teacher's dick is getting hard.
しかも先生のチンコは固くなっていく
Hey, it's not Sugepe-san.
ちょっと、すっげぺさんじゃねえ
Soogepe-san.
すっげぺさん
Seriously?
まじで?
What is it?
どうなんだ?
Eh, but have you been there?
え、でも結構じゃ行ってる?
Are 100 people going?
100人とか行ってる?
average number of people.
平均人数
I haven't gone, I haven't gone.
行ってない、行ってない
Maybe 10 people won't go.
10人行かないとか
this.
これ
10 people won't go?
10人行かない?
Quite a lot, but still.
結構多いけどな、それでも
You just turned 18.
18歳になったばっかりでしょ
When was the first time?
初めてしたの、いつの?
Wow, 6th grade.
わぁ、小6
Huh, no.
はぁ、いや
That's a lie, right?
嘘でしょ
How old were you?
何歳の時っけ、それ
Because I'm in 6th grade.
小6だから
Like 12 years old?
12歳とか?
Yeah.
うん
Eh, can't you do that?
え、ってできへんの?
Yeah.
うん
Who did you do it with?
誰としたの?
Jek person.
ジェクの人
Jake's friend?
ジェクの友達?
A teacher of how to learn.
習い方の先生
gentlemen?
先生?
How old are you?
何歳?
university student.
大学生
Let's play lolicon.
ロリコンやろうじゃん
Didn't it hurt?
痛くなかった?
Did you enter?
入った?
Chincheng.
チンチェン
how was it?
どうだった?
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
It didn't hurt.
痛くなかった
Oh, amazing.
あ、すっごい
Huge?
でっか
nice.
いい ね
I think I'll be Jeku's teacher at elementary school.
小学校んじゃ、ジェクの先生やろうかな
terrible.
やばい
terrible?
やばい?
When I was about 12 years old, my oppa was big.
12歳ぐらいの時はこれ、オッパ大きかったな、
As expected.
やっぱ
It turned out to be D.
Dとかなった
Seriously?
マジで?
He's an adult.
大人だね
Huh, how many of these do you have now?
え、今これいくつあるの?
Wow, G.
わぁ、G
Let's hurry up a bit.
ちょっとさっさくじゃあさ
What is this lewd underwear?
何このスケベ下着?
Hey, are you okay?
ちょ、いいの?
show me.
見せて
What is this lewd underwear?
何 このスケベ下着?
It's really cute though.
めっちゃ可愛いんだけど
Asuka Kirara.
アスカキララ
Asuka Kirara brand.
アスカキララのブランド
Is it the Asuka Kirara brand?
アスカキララブランドなの?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Well, look!
もうだって、見て
I can't get into this anymore.
もう入りきれないくなってるよ、これ
Eh, this is a school uniform, right?
え、これさ、学校制服でしょ?
Are you going to wear something like this?
こういうのつけるの?
What, are you going to school like this?
え、学校これで行ってんの?
She's an incredible woman.
とんでもない女だね
Let's drink a lot of this, Jeku-sensei.
これ、ジェクの先生いっぱい飲んでしよう、
this.
これ
School uniform.
学校制服
Are you drinking a lot?
いっぱい飲んでる?
be drunk
飲まれる
Will you be drunk?
飲まれるの?
Yes, it will be drunk.
うん、飲まれる
It's okay, I have a mother.
いいよ、お母さんいるのに
That's a bad teacher.
悪い先生だね
Well, really.
ね、ほんと
hey.
ね
It's insanely soft.
めちゃめちゃ柔らかい
He already wants to come out.
もう、出たがってるもんね
It's scary, after all, underwear.
怖いね、やっぱね、下着が
Are you going to touch this on one side?
これ、一面で触ったりするの?
Did you really forget?
ほんと忘れ?
a little bit.
ちょっと
why?
なんで?
Why is it noisy?
なんでうるせいんだろう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Because it's embarrassing?
恥ずかしいから?
But wouldn't it be better to have someone touch you?
でも、誰かに触られる方がいいでしょ?
Cute, nice clothes.
かわいいさ、上の服さ
nice.
いいね
I want to take a closer look.
もっとよく見たい
It's amazing how big you are even though you're so thin.
痩せてんのにさ、そんなでかいってすごいよね
Loin, I'm not loining
ロイン、ロインしてないの
To.
に
Will I get this big if I only eat tourist food?
観 光料理ばかり食べるとこんな大きくなるの?
Isn't that so?
そういうわけじゃない?
It's like a meat bun.
肉まんみたい
It looks like a meat bun.
肉まんみたいだね
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいよね
That's amazing.
すげえべだね
This is amazing.
これすげえすげえなんだね
I'm jumpy.
びくびくしてる
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてるよ
It's got a lot of stains.
すごいしみになってんじゃ
yeah.
ん
That's it, ah, start a company.
それ さ、あ、会社立ってさ
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてる
why?
なんで?
Why do you have a cold?
なんで風邪してるの?
I have a cold.
風邪してる
Like this?
こういう風に?
You look thin.
痩せてるね
You're so skinny...
痩せててこの...
That's amazing.
すごいね
amazing.
すごい
It's just so delicious.
ちょうどうまんこいね
Look!
見てごらん
So beautiful.
めっちゃきれい
pink...
ピンク...
Pink pussy.
ピンクうまんこ
It doesn't seem to be used at all.
全然使ってなさそうだけど
Do you spend a lot of time with your teacher?
先生といっぱいしてるの?
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
へー